Guide to the Cornell Center for Materials Research records, 1970-2008
Cornell Center for Materials Research records
- Series IV. Committees
  - Subseries IVb: Visiting
    - Visitors' Review of the Materials Research Laboratory Program, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Directory- Interagency Materials Group, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - MRL Directors' Meeting, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Indirect Cost Committee, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Reverse Site Visit Report- Part I, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Reverse Site Visit Report- Part II, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Center Directors' Meetings, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - MSC Site Visit- Program & Letters, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Materials Review Committee, 1993,1994 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Eastman Kodak Visit, Corning Visit, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Site Visit, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - MRSEC Directors' Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Visiting Committee Meetings, Jul 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Singapore Delegation, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - MRSEC Directors' Meetings, 2000-2005 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Facility Managers' Meeting, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Site Visit, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Pomeroy Equipment, Program Announcement, Facilities Files, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Reverse Site Visit, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Series V. Programs
  - Subseries Va: Research Experience for Undergraduates
    - REU Treasure Hunt, Project Listing, Applicant Listing, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - REU Annual Progress Summary, Application Forms, Welcome Package, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - REU Attendance List, Computer Account, Correspondence, Picnic, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - DOD- Instrumentation, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - REU Farewell Brochure, Faculty Email Feedback, Schedule, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - REU Fun Talks, General Info, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - REU Housing Lab Safety, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - REU General Info., 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - REU Correspondence, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - REU General Info., Correspondence, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - REU Visits, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - REU Timeline, Trips, T-Shirts, Web Pages, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - REU Student Survey, Interviews, Faculty Surveys, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - REU Stipend Info, Group Photos, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - REU Treasure Hunt, Application Listing, Mailing List, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - REU Info, Policy Statement, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - REU Program Highlights, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - REU Fun Tales, Correspondence, Forums, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - REU Program- Advertisement/Letters, Evaluation, Forms, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - REU General Info., 1995 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - REU/REM Fun Talks, Final Report, Project Listing, Comments, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - REU General Info., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - REU Photos, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - REU Program Info., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - REU Program Info., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - REU Program Info., 1991 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - REU Program Info., 1990 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - REU Program Info., 1989 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - REU Special Reports, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - REU Contracts and Budgets, 1998-2005 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - REU Program, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - REU Program (Fall & Summer), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - REU Program (Fall & Summer), 1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - REM (Research Experience for Minorities), 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - REU Program, Summer 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - REU Program, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - REU Program, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - REU Program, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - REU Highlights, Photos, Summer 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - REU Program Info, Photos, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - REU Project Descriptions, Publication Info., Selection Board, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - REU Research Summary, Research Presentations, Stipend & Tax Info., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - REU Application Lists, Library Privileges, Meal Plans, Mini Courses, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - REU Research Summaries, Summer 1999 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - REU Program Info/Activities, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - REU Activities, Projects, Schedules, Applicant Info., 1999 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - REU Surveys, Letters to Profs., Faculty Evals., 1999 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - REU Catering, T-shirt, Annual Report, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - REU Detailed Agenda, Annual Report, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - REU Attendance List, Application, BBQ Flyer, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - REU Calender, Correspondence, Housing, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - REU Meetings, Mini-Course, Surveys, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - REU Orientations/Presentations, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - REU Presentations, Research Booklet, Statistics, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - REU Research Summaries, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - REU Information/Statistics, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - REU Surveys, Thank-You's, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - REU Treasure Hunt, T-shirts, Web Pages, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - REU Agenda, Annual Reports, Correspondence, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - REU Information Notebook, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - REU Application Form, Attendance, BBQ, Facilities Tour, Fun Talk, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - REU Planning, Housing, Info Package, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - REU RA Info, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - REU Mini-Courses, Info Packet, Project Info, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - REU Timeline, Thank You T-shirts, Youra Workship, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - REU Student/Faculty Surveys, Interviews, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - REU Report Photos, Research Presentations, Statistics, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - REU Participants' Research Summaries, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - REU T-shirts, Timelines, Trips, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - REU Student Survey, Interview, Faculty Survey, Pictures, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - REU Sorority, Stipends Presentation, Workshops, Participant List, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - REU Participant Research Summaries, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - REU Orientation, Agenda, Participant List, Misc., Minicourses, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - REU Fun Talks, Mails, Fellowships/Scholarships, Email Addresses, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - REU Schedule, Attendance List, BBQ, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - REU Sorority Info., 2003 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - REU Research Summaries, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - REU Presentations Workshoops, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - REU Mini Courses, Misc., Info., Packet, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - REU Flyer, Mailing Databases, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - REU Facilities Tour, Faculty Solicitation, Fun Talks, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - REU Application, Info., BBQ, Webpages, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Reverse Site Visit, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - REU Proposal, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - REU Proposal, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - REU/RET Proposal, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - REU Historical Summaries (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - ROA Proposal- Tanenbaum, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - REU/RET Publications List, 1989-1998 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - REU Supplement, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - REU Prior Proposals, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - REU Proposals, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - REU Report &Survey, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - REU Research Summary, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - REU Info, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - REU Info (Research Summary, Sample Survey & Interview), 2003 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - REU Program Info., 2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - REU- Research Summaries, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - REU Program Info., 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - REU Info Package, Report, Attendee List, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - REU Program Info., 1997 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - REU Program- Research Summaries, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - REU Announcement, 1996-1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - REU Program Activities, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - REU Program Info., 1993 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - REU Program Info., 1992 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - REU Program Info., 1991 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - REU Reports, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - REU Reports, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - REU Reports, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - REU Program Info., 1991 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - REU Program Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - REU Info. Package, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - REU Program Info., 1998 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - REU Program Info., 1997 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - REU Program Info., 1996 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - REU Program Info., 1995 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - REU Program Info., 1994 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - 2001 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Subseries Vb: Research Experience for Teachers
    - RET Proposal, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Research Experience for Teachers Proposal, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - RET Info., 1999 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - RET Handbook for Teachers, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - RET Proposal, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - RET Info, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - RET Annual Report, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - RET Info (Report, Handbook etc.), 2004 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Subseries Vc: Materials Research Science and Energy Center
    - MRSEC Press Releases Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - MRSEC Wrap-Up Package (Reviews), Jan 2000 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - MRSEC Renewal- Review Material, Jan 2000 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - MRSEC Renewals- Strawman Budget, SEEDS Descriptions, Emerging Areas, Reviewer Info., Rebuttals, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - MRSEC Reverse Site Visit & Panel Recommendations, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Retention of Records, 1992-1999 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Reprints- Physical Review Letters (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Radiation Safety, Rawlings-Letter, Patents, 1996-2000 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - CCMR Office Retreat, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Lowe-Letter, MSC/CCMR Charter, Nuggets, 1968-2000 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Office Gov't Affairs, Herbert H. Johnson Memorial Lectures, Prof. R. Friend Seminar, 1999-2001 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Simmons Sub Award, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters- Educational Outreach (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Materials World Module Info., 2002 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - NSF Site Review, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - MRL Symposium, MRL Meeting, 1985,1991 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - NSF/NSB Review of MRL's Memorandum to NSB Members, 1980,1979 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - NSF Advisory Council, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Memorandum to NSB Members, MRL - Summary Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - 1974-1985 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Memorandum to NSB Members, MRL Program Recommendations, MSC Exec. Committee Memo, 1974-1985 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - NSF- Advisory Subcommittee for MRL, Nov 1979 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Memorandum to NSB Members, MRL Program Recommendations, MSC. Exec. Committee Memo, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Interdisciplinary Materials Research - Proposals (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Memorandum to NSB Members, 1974-1977 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Interdisciplinary Materials Research - Proposals (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Memorandum to NSB Members, NSF Thrust Areas, 1974-1977 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence-CCMR-General, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - MRL Program- Research Highlights, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - MRL Program- Research Highlights, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - MRSEC Continuation Awards, 1997-2001 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - MRSEC Org Supplement, Lou Hand Awards, MRI Award, REU-Site, 1999-2006 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - MRSEC Award, RET Award, 2000-2006 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - CCMR Office Events/Meetings, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Grant Info, 1995-1999 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Annual Meeting- MSC Members, 1961-1991 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - MSC Annual Report Originals, Job Descriptions- Accounts Assistant, 1963-1994 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Job Descriptions- Sr. Research Assoc I (Brock), 1975-1994 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Job Description- Research Technician, 1961-1983 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Job Descriptions- Research Technician, 1961-1983 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - MRSEC Final Panel Recommendations, Manager Low Temp Facility, UHV Stem, Senior Research Assoc., 1975-1996 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - URL Policies & Procedures- Corresp., MRL Review Mechanisms and Guidelines, 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Continuation Requirements, MRSEC Website, Microscopy Facility - McCrone, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - MRSEC Presentations, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - MRSEC Presentations, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - MRSEC Presentations, 2000-2002 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Reverse Site Visit- Panel Report, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Reverse Site Visit- Reviewers Analysis, Panelists Info., 2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Reverse Site Visit, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - MRSEC Renewal Submission, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - MRSEC Renewal Submission, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - MRSEC Renewal Info., 1999 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - MRSEC Renewal Budget, Jan 2000 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - MRSEC Renewals- Facilities, Competition Summary, Jan 2000 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - MRSEC Renewals- Achievements, Jan 2000 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - History of Center Renewal Activities, 1998-2000 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Proposal for a Materials Research Science and Engineering Center, Jan 2000 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - MRSEC Renewals- Meetings, Nov 1999, Jan 2000 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - MRSEC-Renewals - Mail Reviews, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - MRSEC Renewals- Letters, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - MOU- Hudson Mesoscale Processing Facility, CCMR Members' Accounts, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - G-Line Personnel- Corresp. Funding Opps/Agencies, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - CCMR- Final Report DMR- 9632275, 1996-2000 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - NSF/MRSEC Miscellaneous, MRSEC Brochure-Corresp. MRSEC Awards, CCMR IRG Proposals, 1998-2004 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - CCMR Outreach Program Meeting, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Donations to Center, Sproull etc.-Info, 2001-2005 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - MRSEC Research Highlights, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee, Jul 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Subseries Vd: Industry Programs
    - Hartman Book Project- Corresp., 2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Penn State Collaboration-CCMR, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Sproull Fund Correspondence, 2001, 2004, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Research Support- Frank (Corresp.), 2004,2006 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Tuskegee Prem/Weisner Proposal- Info and Corresp., 2005 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Assitance in Areas of National Need, 2006-2007 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Fuel Cell Institute- Correspondence, Contracts and Budgets, 2003-2007 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Future Energy Systems, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - NY State Office of Science, Technology & Academic Research (NYSTAR)- Contract Info., 2004-2006 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - IGERT Program, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Exec. Committee Capital, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Educational Outreach University; FDP Subaward Agreement, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Intership (MPS-IPSE) Awards, Cornell Institute for Chemistry Teachers, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - IRG-C Allocation- Ashcroft, Baker, Dieckmann, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Photonic Building Blocks-Webb, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - SEED- Atomic Scale Elect. Order-Disorder, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - SFA Contract- Harold S., 2001-2003 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Contracts & Budgets- NYSTAR etc., 2003-2007 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Educational Outreach Newsletters and "Emerging Education" - an Overview of NSF's Materials Research Science and Engineering Centers (2004), Oct. 1999; Nov. 2001, March 2004, Summers 2005, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Alliance for Manufacturing and Technology, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Polymer Outreach Program- Revlon, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Phonon Scattering Conference, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Solid State Sciences Forum, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Outreach at Cornell University- Plan Personnel, 1990, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - IBM Workbench Corresp., 1987-1991, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - IBM Workbench Related Corresp., 1989, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Workbench (IBM) Toolkit-Corresp., 1990 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Contract- Polymer Outreach Program (POP), 2002-2007 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - INFO- LOU HAND, 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Universal Instruments, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - POP-Nanomat, Kodak, UOP LLC, Rockwell Scientific, 2003,2005 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - POP- UDR, GM, UAS JOO, 2002, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Corson Luncheon, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - HOU's, NDA-NSF DiSalvo, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - MRL Workshops- Corresp., 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - MITRE Study- Info, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Surface Science Seminar Records (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Polymer Outreach Program Info., 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Industrial Outreach, National Science Board Policy, Facilities, Diversity, Budget, Response Mail Reviews, Publications, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Capital Equipment Budget Sheets, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - IRG-C Plans, IRG-D, IRG-E- Capital Equip., 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SPS New, Exec. Committee Meeting, CCMR Policy Library, Capital Equipment, 2000, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Dawson Conference, Zoom EC Capital, XPS Systems Kodak Donation, New NCORA Folder, 2005-2007 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - GM NUTOLO, Pomeroy Equip., Graduate Assistance in Areas of National Need (GAANN), 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - HINES-NSTAR, GAANN (DOE), 2000, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - GAANN Fellowships, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Wiesner/Warren Star Fellowship, Baker-Materials Research Society, Schember NASA/USRA, NSF LOU HAND, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Williams NYSTAR, Dawson NSF Development of Accel. Method, Giannelis Serisui Chem., 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Malliaras NSF, Coca-Cola Schember, 3-IU, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - GAANN: Synthesis and Behaviour of Mats at Ultra Pressure- DOE, Reverse Site Visit, 2002,2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Sciencenter Exhibits, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - MSC Outreach Programs, Build-A-Microscope, High School Workshop, 1982, 1995, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Microworld Festival Workshop, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - K-12 Committee, Institiute for the Academic Advancement of Youth, 1995, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - POP- Nissan, Wisner, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Collaborative Workshop, KDI-Clancy/Nev, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Significant Accomplishments- IDL, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Project- ARPA (by Union Carbide, Cornell), Info-NASA Visit, 1964, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - MRL- George Keyworth, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - MITRE Corp. MRL Program Study, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Acknowledgement Support Statements (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Institute for the Academic Advancement of Youth (IAAY), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - K-12 Outreach Evaluations, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Microworld Extension Activities Info., 1998 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Research Symposium (Graduate Student and Postdoc.), Jun 2007 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Polymer Outreach, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Polymer Day, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Mechanical Properties, Surface Science, 1974-1986 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Optical Phenomena, Phase Transitions, 1974-1995 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Thin Film and Interfaces Seminar, 1977-1982 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Defect Structures, Energy Transfer, Polymers Study Group, Small Particles Study Group, 1976-1977, 1981, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - New Solid State Materials, Theory & Modelling, Msc 1994-1995 Annual Report Photos, 1976-1995 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Brookhaven Project, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Symposium on Surfaces and Interfaces, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Tuskegee University Collaboration, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Information- Next Generation Ion Beam, Analysis- US Army Research Office, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - CCMR Poster Board, POP Administration, POP Tuition, Industry Surveys, Short Courses, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - CSE Engineering Conference, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Susan O'Conner Presentation, Empire State Dev. Corp., VP Research, 2000, 2004-2005 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Polymer Outreach Program- 8th Annual Symposium, Directory- Interagency Materials Group, 1990,1997 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - US Custom Service- Corresp. (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Xerox Wilson Center, Corning Inc. Science & Technology, Lobby Letters to Representatives, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Bill to Advance National Technology Foundation (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - SSSP- National Research Council, 1980's (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Write-Up on CCMR, Proposal-Biomaterials, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Nano Bio Overlap, Simmons Proposal, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Special Reports, NSF Funding Info., 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Central Facilities Review Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Subseries Ve: Lectures and Presentations
    - MSC lecture series, M. Cohen, reel 1, 1962-1963; 8287 (Box 40)
    - MSC lecture series, M. Cohen, reel 2, 1962-1967; 8288 (Box 40)
    - Various presentations, 8 videos, 1990s; 1432-1439 (Box 40)
    - Short Course on Nanonscience, Lockheed Martin Knolls Atomic Power Lab, January 2002; 434 (Box 40)
- Series VI. Facilities
  - MSC High Temperature Facility Info., 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Science & Technology Center, Kodak Coupling, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Clark/Baker Computing Facility, 1968-1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Acquisition of Clark/Baker Computing System, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Facility Info., 1992-1994 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Dynamitron Info./Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 3.0 Mev Dynamitron Info., 1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Patents, 1965-1970 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Ultramet NDA, Facility MOU's, NDA for UTC, 2004,2006 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Umbach Facility Info., Acquisition of Energy Filter, 2003,2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports- Facilities, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Central Facilities Equipment Request (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Master Plan for ENGG. Facilities at Cornell, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - General Center Info.- MSC, 1990's (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - MSC Computing Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Advisory Committee- Computing Facility at MSC, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Computing-Microwave Link with License (Clark Hall) (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - X-ray Crystallography - Computing Facility (Technical Proposal), 1978 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Array Processor- Materials Processor Center, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Materials Science Center- Theory Center, 1986-1991 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - MSC Theory Center- Supercomputer, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - MSC Computing Facility Upgrade, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Addition to Computing Facility- MSC, 1980-1984 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Multi-User Computer Facility- MSC, 1977-1984 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Convex Project Final Report, MRSEC-Thurston Hall, 1991,1984 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Acquisition of Advanced Computing Equipment for Experimental Materials Science- Budget Details, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - MSC Advisory Committee on Computers, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - MSC Computer Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - MSC Computer Usage Survey, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - MSC Computer Committee (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - IBM Workstation Project, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 31)